theiphoneappreview.com 2018-02-25

# Privacy Policy, Email & Consumer Disclosure Information | TheiPhoneAppReview.com

The following is important Consumer Disclosure Information as well as the official privacy policy for TheiPhoneAppReview.com , a website centered around reviewing smartphone applications. This Privacy Policy covers the issues related to personal information collected by the site and information regarding tracking and information collection from our affiliates, advertisers and partners.

**Collection of Personal Information** – At TheiPhoneAppReview.com, we recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important and we take every measure to keep you informed on how we collect, safeguard and use your personal data, where applicable. We never sell your personal information to third parties, however our site might run scripts (such as Google Analytics) that collect log file information for analytical and statistical reports. The kind of information these third parties collect include your IP address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider), the browser you visit our site with (Firefox, Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Safari, etc), the pages you visit and the time you spend on pages of our site. This information is used strictly for ourselves, using it to better improve our site’s performance and user experience. We will never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Cookies and Web Beacons** – Cookies are small text files that are placed in the visitor’s computer with the purpose of storing their preferences. Cookies cannot damage user files, nor can they read information from a user’s hard drive, they are purely “shortcuts” that allow web sites to remember users activities on a web site as well as users visits to a site. Since we use third party advertisements to support TheiPhoneAppReview.com, there is a chance the companies running these ads might store your data in cookies, in order to collect advertisement information or protect you from abusive advertising (for example, stopping pop-up scripts from running multiple times from your IP). Because these advertisement companies may also collect the personal information stated above, we at TheiPhoneAppReview.com make sure we only use trustworthy 3rd parties, in order to protect our users.

In general, these cookies and web beacons are used for research purposes and for geo-targeting and behavioral targeting of the ads. If you feel uncomfortable providing this kind of information to our advertisers through cookies, you can turn them off from your preferred browser’s settings, or manage them through Internet Security software (such as Norton Internet Security for example).

TheiPhoneAppReview.com displays adverts on all of our pages, from Google Adsense and other app developers. These Advertisers offers safe targeted ads to our users.

If there are any inappropriate adverts displayed we would kindly ask you to contact us so we can investigate further.

Google is also using the DART cookie to collect information about every user. This cookie does not store any personal data or sensitive information and can be removed by you searching the cookie in the cookies folder of your browser on your PC

**External Links** – Our site has several external links pointing to our partners, or the iPhone apps we post on our site might have links to other sites that might offer content that we have no control over. Unfortunately, we cannot take responsibility for the content shown by our partners, although we only pick to link to related, quality websites that are non-intrusive and offer clean content suitable for our target audience.

**Affiliated Links** – We strive to be fully compliant with all FTC regulations pertaining to full disclosure to our readers. We work with VigLink and our Full Disclosure about our affiliate relationship can be found [here](http://www.viglink.com/legal/disclosures/users).

**Paid Reviews** – We post reviews that we do not receive any compensation for, and we also post reviews that have been expedited for a fee or are part of a larger paid marketing package. That being said, we pride ourselves on our completely objective reviews. Our ratings are never influenced by whether or not a fee has been paid or if a review is part of a larger paid marketing package. Our reviewers are never told if an expedite fee has been paid or if a review is part of a larger paid marketing package. When any compensation has been received by us in connection with a review or press release we post the following note at the end of the post: “ _A small expedite fee was paid to speed up the publication of this review.”_

**Email Opt-In** – By contacting us in any way, including the various submission forms on this site, you agree to receive outbound email. If you filled in a form on this site the first email you receive will likely be a reply to your submission. If you receive an outbound marketing email you will have **the option of opting out** so that you would not receive any emails after that. We will only send emails on an occasional basis and will remove you from our email list if you ever decide to opt out.

**Parents –** We do not collect any personal information such as age, location, etc. We also do not employ a chat room or private messaging service on this website.

**Copyright –** We post iPhone apps for all ages. The copyright of these apps are the sole property of their creators as we do not claim to have any rights upon the apps.

If you think that someone is using your work and has stolen your creation please use the contact form in our contact page and write us a message containing the link to the page where you saw this copyright abuse and we will take immediate action to delete the app review and report it to the proper authorities.

All the iPhone apps published on TheiPhoneAppReview.com must follow the above rule and we can’t be held responsible if those requirements are not met.  
**  
By accessing TheiPhoneAppReview.com and using this website, you consent with this Privacy Policy and you agree to be banned without any warnings if you are reported of missuse of our rules and terms. If you do not agree with our policy we politely ask you to stop using our system. You also agree that we may at any time change the contents of this Privacy Policy without any announcement.**
